1

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains how we process your personal data when you use our Website, pinkfloyd.com (Website). If you haveany questions or comments about this privacy policy, please let us know by email to privacy@pinkfloyd.com.

The Website is operated by Pink Floyd (1987) Limited (we, us, our) a company incorporated in England \& Wales, on behalf of PinkFloyd (1987) Limited and Pink Floyd Music Limited (PFM). Accordingly, we will share your personal information with PFM, anaffiliate of ours, who may also use your personal information in the same way as us. Where we decide the purpose or means forthe processing of the personal data that you provide when using our Website, we are the “data controller” for the purposes of theGeneral Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This policy should be read together with our Terms \& Conditions of the Website.

Our Website may contain hyperlinks to third party websites. These websites operate fully independently from us, and we cannotaccept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third parties nor the availability of these external sites orresources. The appearance of such links on our Website is not an endorsement. Should you use any of these websites, such use isat your own risk and we would recommend that you review their respective privacy policies.

1. How we use your personal data

Mailing List

If you ask to be added to our mailing list, we will keep you updated with information on news, releases, tour dates,merchandise and pre-sales by email unless you would like to be removed from that list (in which case please letus know by clicking unsubscribe at the bottom of any marketing email that you receive). In order to send you theinformation that is most relevant to your location, we may also ask you to tell us which country you are in.

In line with the legitimate interest we have in promoting our business, we will use the email address you gave usvia our Website to provide you with this information.

There may also be circumstances where we will ask you for your explicit consent in respect of our use of yourdata in which case you will be notified at the time.

Your Enquiries

If you contact us about our services, the forms you complete or the emails you send may include informationabout you, such as your name as the contact point for an organisation, your email address, the organisation'saddress and your enquiry. We use this information to respond to your enquiries.

 In line with the legitimate interest we have in promoting our business, we will process your enquiries to replyand provide you with information about the services we offer.

 We may also process enquiries to take steps you ask of us with a view to entering into an agreement toprovide you with our services.

 You are under no obligation to provide us with any details, but if you don’t provide all relevant information,we may not be able to help.

Any user generated forum or bulletin board

If you create an account for any public forum or bulletin board we may operate in the future, we may ask you toprovide the following information, namely your:

 username (mandatory);

 password (mandatory)

 date of birth;

 location (country);

 occupation; and

 avatar;

and/or such other information as we may request (as indicated on the forum) or you voluntarily submit to thepublic forum.

We may process this information so you are able to use the forum, in accordance with the terms of use agreedbetween us.

2

How you use our Website (Analytics)

Our Website uses cookies and other mechanisms, such as third party pixels and Google Tag manager, to collect

analytical information, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, to help analyse how visitors use the Website.

 We process this information to understand how visitors use our Website and to compile statistical reports

regarding that activity (for example, your IP address is used to approximate the country from which you

access our Website, and we aggregate this information together so we know that, for example, that visitors

to our Website come from a specific territory). This information is not used by us to develop a personal

profile of you.

 We or other companies may use cookies to suggest and deliver content which we believe may interest you.

Some of our webpages may use plug-ins from other organisations (such as Google, Facebook and Spotify).

These other organisations may use information about your visit to our Websites on their pages. For more

information on how these organisations use information, please read their privacy policies.

 This processing is necessary for us to pursue our legitimate interests in improving our Website, and

providing a better service and source of information to visitors.

You can always choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. By default, most internet browsers

accept Cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet

browser. For further information about cookies, please see: www.allaboutcookies.org, and how to adjust your

browser settings here: www.allaboutcookies.org/managecookies.

Google Analytics

We may use Google Analytics on our Website for anonymous reporting of Website usage If you would like to opt-

out of Google Analytics monitoring your behaviour on our Website please use this link

(https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ )

All content you submit to us

If you send us objectionable content or otherwise behave in a disruptive manner when using our Website, we may

process personal data included in your messages to respond to and stop such behaviour.

 We only process personal data in this way for the legitimate interests of ensuring that use of our Website is

lawful, does not disrupt our systems, does not harass our staff or other individuals, and to enforce our legal

rights and to comply with our legal obligations.

 Where we reasonably believe you are or may be in breach of the law (for instance, because content you

send amounts to harassment or is defamatory), we may use your personal information to inform relevant

third parties such as your email/internet provider or law enforcement agencies about the content.

 Where we process personal data in this way, we will hold that personal information on our systems for as

long as is reasonably necessary to achieve these objectives.

Purchases

We do not offer any direct sales via our Website. Any purchases you make on the websites listed below are

operated by third parties and subject to their terms and conditions and privacy policy. We recommend that you

review these.

When you purchase products or services related to Pink Floyd, our commercial partners may, following your

consent, provide your information to us, so that you can be added to our mailing list (see relevant section above).

2. Do we share your personal information with anyone else?

We keep your information confidential, but may disclose it to our personnel, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as it is reasonablynecessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, provided that they do not make independent use of the information.

We only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions. All our thirdparty service providers are required to take appropriate security measures to protect your personal information in line with ourpolicies. Activities which are carried out by third party service providers include: CRM management software, website hosting, andIT support.

In addition, we may disclose your information to the extent that we are required to do so by law (which may include to governmentbodies and law enforcement agencies); in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; and toestablish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention).

3

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our business or assets, the information we hold may beincluded as part of that sale, in which case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Website of any changesin ownership or use of your information, as well as any choices you may have regarding that information.

Except as provided above, we will not provide your information to third parties.

3. Your rights in relation to personal data which we process relating to you

You have the following rights over the way we process personal data relating to you. We aim to comply without undue delay inresponse to any requests by you:

 for a copy of data we are processing about you and have inaccuracies corrected;

 to restrict, stop processing, or to delete your personal data;

 for a machine readable copy of your personal data, which you can use with another service provider. Where it is technicallyfeasible, you can ask us to send this information directly to another provider if you prefer; and

 to make a complaint to a data protection regulator.

Please send your requests to privacy@pinkfloyd.com.

4. Children

We do not use the Website to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomesaware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us atprivacy@pinkfloyd.com. We will delete such information within a reasonable time.

5. Security

We will take all reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss misuse or alteration of your personalinformation.

6. Changes

This policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new policy here and, wherefeasible, by letting you know by email.

7. International Data Transfers

Some information we hold may be stored on servers that may be located outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Withcertain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data thesame protection it has in Europe.

Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them toprovide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US.

If you would like to find out more about these safeguards, please let us know by writing to privacy@pinkfloyd.com.

8. Retention Periods

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant purpose, or as otherwisedescribed in this privacy policy.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personaldata, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process yourpersonal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
